import "Catalog/catalog.css";
import "Catalog/en/english-language/colors/style.css";

// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],
}


export var cards = {
  '0': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Zero',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'zéro'
  },
  '1': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'One',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'un'
  },
  '2': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Two',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'deux'
  },
  '3': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Three',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'trois'
  },
  '4': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Four',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'quatre'
  },
  '5': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Five',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'cinq'
  },
  '6': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Six',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'six'
  },
  '7': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Seven',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'sept'
  },
  '8': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Eight',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'huit'
  },
  '9': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Nine',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'neuf'
  },
  '10': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Ten',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'dix'
  },
  '11': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Eleven',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'onze'
  },
  '12': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Twelve',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'douze'
  },
  '13': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Thirteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'treize'
  },
  '14': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Fourteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'quatorze'
  },
  '15': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Fifteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'quinze'
  },
  '16': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Sixteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'seize'
  },
  '17': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Seventeen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'dix-sept'
  },
  '18': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Eighteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'dix-huit'
  },
  '19': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Nineteen',
    prompt: 'Translate in French?',
    answer: 'dix-neuf'
  }
};